doity day
squid.
>> All right, I think it's time we go back
to the office.
>> I love everything. I love life. I love
everything. I love
>> Okay, stop, please. It's kind of
annoying now.
>> But I love
>> swim. Being positive is good, but
there's a time and a place. You behaved
pretty bad with Mr. Ice Cream back
there.
>> I'm not trying to be mean. I'm just, you
know, I'm just saying.
>> Oh, I see. I I I get it, Pim. I get it.
I wasn't being positive at all. I'm
going to help this couple. I'm going to
help this wheel. I'm going to help this
homeless thing.
>> Swim, calm down.
>> Oh, I got to help those police over
there with whatever they're doing.
>> Swim, get back here.
>> Sir, get on the ground.
>> Get on the ground, MAN. GET ON THE
GROUND.
>> SIR, we have you surrounded.
>> OH MY GOSH. CHARLIE,
>> DANCE. Everybody doing the swim dance.
>> HE'S DOING THE SWIM DANCE. SHOOT HIM.
>> Stop shooting. Shots fired. Shots fired.
>> Do a little square. Make a little love.
Get down.
>> You really proved your loyalty to me,
Charlie. Everything ended up working out
in the end.
>> Except for Squim. I feel terrible about
what happened to him.
>> What do you mean? Squim's soul just went
through a 14-hour surgery. He's going to
live.
>> Hello there.
>> I'm sorry. Who Who is Who is this? He
was like the first smiling friend I ever
hired. Uh used to be like really wacky
and stuff. Pim could back me up.
>> Yeah, he was. Yeah.
>> Yeah. If you saw him before, it'd make
more sense.
>> Uh okay.
[music]